Gkouvousis Nektarios

+30 6988896560 | gouvousisnektarios@gmail.com | Kallithea, Attica

Summary

Creative and hard-working full-stack software engineer with 2 years of experience in backend technologies like C# and .NET framework, Java, Python & MySQL . Entry level knowledge of web development. Currently studying Informatics and Computer Engineering at University of Western Attica. You can find more about me at my personal github page or my personal web site

GitHub: https://github.com/Gouvo7

Web Page: https://gouvo7.github.io/Personal Web Page/

Experience

DataBlue S.A. | Athens, Attica

Junior Full Stack Developer | 11/2023 - Present

Development of a desktop application that provides multiple tools for doctors to help them with their job by communicating with Web Services. Software stack and technologies used alongside .NET: Entity, SQLite, MongoDB, MVVM, JavaScript/Ajax, XML, HTML5, JSON, Javascript

Niro Technologies | Athens, Attica

Data Engineer / Software Development | 10/2022 - 11/2023

SQL database development, maintenance, data analysis, and creation of efficient automated tasks and procedures for client's needs using MySQL scripts. Maintenance and update of a CRM built on C# using .NET framework. Created automated tasks using Python scripts.

VirtualNet | Athens, Attica

Computer Hardware Technician | 03/2022 - 10/2022

Installation of embedded systems for automated parking solutions. Technical support for customers facing software/hardware issues. Debug software for applications provided with the embedded systems (C/C++, C#, Pvthon).

Vodafone Group | Athens, Attica

Sales Advisor and Tech Expert I 07/2020 - 07/2021

Providing solutions based on customer needs. Promotion of company's products. Smart devices service and repair (smartphones, laptops etc).

Skills

C, C++, C#, Python, SQL, .NET, HTML, Java, CSS, APIS, GIT, Bash, JIRA, Problem Solving, Communication skills, Teamwork, Greek (Fluent), English (Fluent)

Education

University of West Attica | Athens, Attica Informatics and Computer Engineering | 08/2024

Slovak University of Technology | Bratislava

Computer Science | 02/2022

Participation in the Erasmus project for the period September 2021 - February 2022 at Slovak University of Technology in Bratislava

High School of Monemvasia | Monemvasia, Lakonia High school diploma | 06/2018